Contributing 投稿
============
如果增加新的“哈咯，世界”編程語言， 請把該文件命名根據格式。 如果該編程語言不長，請滿名稱地命名如 “JavaScript”，而不是“JS”，如果太長如“Cascading Style Sheets” ,請命名為“CSS”
When adding new "Hello World" programs, please name the file according to the language it was written in, don't abbreviate the language name too much (so use "JavaScript", not "JS") but don't make it TOO long (so use "CSS" not "Cascading Style Sheets". Use hyphens ("-") as word seperators, and only use a single dot (for seperating the filename from the extension). For example, a "Hello World" program in Objective C should be named "Objective-C.m, and the one in HTML should be named HTML.html.

**INPORTANT: IF YOU WANT TO CHANGE THE README (`README.md`), EDIT `README_nolist.md` (!) THEN RUN THE `list_langs.py` SCRIPT AS NOTED BELOW.**
**重要事項 ：如果您想要更改 README ('README.md'),請利用 'README_nolist.md'來進行更改。 然後啟動'list_langs.py'如以下。** 
Use
```bash
./list_langs.py
```
for updating the list of languages in `README.md` (make sure you are in the repository's root directory when running the script). This script will completely re-write `README.md`, copying the contents of `README_nolist.md` before the listing.  
**NOTE THAT THIS SCRIPT MUST BE EXECUTED ON PYTHON 3.6+!** If your default isn't 3.6+, use `python3 list_langs.py`.
更改時請確保您是在存储库的主目錄來使用 'list_langs.py'。 
**記得此編程需使用 PHYTON 3.6++** 如果沒有或不是3。6+版本，請使用 `python3 list_langs.py`。